are you a why me kind of person that's going to be a doozy in trying to move past shit that
happens to you let's take another read of an excerpt from my latest book body waving through
the bs crank that through an essay the essay stands for sexual assault something we humans
have a habit of doing is always looking for the cause and effect of things within frameworks
limited by our egos histories knowledge etc sometimes the answer is right in front of your
face so often though it is not a series of events took place that led to this particular moment
happening this particular way and though there may have been an opportunity to shift it at some
point on the timeline that would have required the other parties to also shift had i plunged into the
why me i would have begun mentally assaulting myself for having left the door unlocked then i'd be angry
at devon for making things awkward and us sleeping apart that night then i'd be angry at the hotel for
not having security then i'd be angry at whatever happened to this person that has them sneaking
into the rooms of strangers and sexually assaulting them then i'd be angry at the country of grenada for
being the place where this man existed it is a never-ending domino effect of anger and blame
none of which will restore my security of self i am in no way saying don't seek out justice and
reparative repercussions when one has been wronged i am also not saying forgive your attacker to set
yourself free fuck that my attacker who unfortunately was never identified and thus not brought to
justice has not asked for forgiveness thus it has not been extended what i am saying is the sooner one
can accept that everything is everything and respond accordingly the smoother they can ease into
their path to recovery you can take responsibility and accountability for aspects of your involvement in
things being able to move forward you know like we are in a series of events that so often feel like
they're just unwieldy and happening outside of our control and so like all you can really do is say
like damn i should have done that and i will do it next time deep tragedies happen because of errors
there are people that are making cognizant choices to harm you have to know how are you moving was a
decision made and intention to harm was there a carelessness that was deeply rooted in something
that you're not addressing was there a naivete i gotta tell you shit happens yo sometimes shit just
happens to happen to really good people to babies and all we can do is our best to stop it
and prevent it what we're unable to do is unfortunately go back in time so for all of us out here who are
dealing with the repercussions of decisions that we would have possibly made differently had we known
you gotta set yourself free you gotta set yourself free to not be stuck in a past you can't change
so that you can be active in changing your present for the future my book body waving through the bs
thank you for supporting my little shop